axxessweb.com 2016-05-11

# Home Health Software | Home Care Software | Axxess

## Axxess Privacy Policy

### Table Of Contents

  1. Scope And Purpose
  2. What Information Do We Collect?
  3. How Do We Use Your Information
  4. Sharing Your Information
  5. Updates To This Privacy Policy
  6. What Else Do You Need To Know?
  7. Key Terms
  8. Contact

**This policy is effective as of May 2015**

### Scope And Purpose

This privacy policy (“the Policy”) describes the practices of Axxess Technology Solutions Inc. (“we,” “us,” or “Axxess”) with regard to information about you that we obtain, either directly or indirectly through third-party vendors, or through www.axxess.com (“the Website”). We do not control and are not responsible for the privacy practices of, or the data available on, the websites of third parties, and we urge you to evaluate the soundness of these practices for yourself. 

### What Information Do We Collect?

The Following Types of information may be collected on the Website: 

  * We may collect information you provide us if you sign up for or request certain services from us on our Website. If you are interested in learning more about Axxess and the services and products we offer, we will ask for your name, company name, role, email address, telephone number, and address.
  * We may collect your IP address and other data about the equipment used to visit the Website, the patterns of searching and browsing that preceded access to the Website, and the patterns of searching and browsing on the Website. 

The Website does not responde to web browsers' Do Not Track signals. 

### How Do We Use Your Information?

We use information collected through tracking technologies, such as cookies and web beacons, to improve the functionality of the Website. For example: 

  * We track the number of visitors using certain portions or features of the Website to make changes that may be necessary to improve the Website’s functionality;
  * We track the popularity of features on the Website to guide the development of new ones;
  * We assess the ways in which users become aware of or access the Website in order to gauge the quality and methods of our advertising.

If you choose to provide Axxess with personally identifiable information, we will use that information for our internal business purposes only. For example: 

  * If you provide us with your email address, we may use it for our own marketing, promotional, and informational purposes, including solicitations, invitations, newsletters, awareness campaigns, and announcements, but we will not share your email address with unaffiliated third parties.

### Sharing Your Information

We engage certain service providers for purposes of tracking and associating internet search and browsing behavior with our advertisements and to provide functionality on the Website. We enable them to use tracking technologies, such as cookies and web beacons, on or in conjunction with the Website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to other websites, together with non-personally identifiable information about your purchases and interests from other online and offline sources, to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you. The use and collection of information by these service providers is governed by their respective privacy statements and thus, is not covered by this Policy. In addition, we may share Website usage information with these service providers to manage and target ads and for market research purposes. Finally, information obtained through these processes may be combined with personally identifiable information in order to analyze our marketing efforts. 

Please note that Axxess will only share your information in accordance with this Policy, except in the following situations: 

  * You have given us your consent to share or use information about you;
  * We believe that we need to share information about you to provide a service that you have requested from us or from others;
  * We are required by law to disclose information; or
  * We believe that it is necessary to protect our rights or to avoid liability or violations of the law.

### Updates To This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make periodic updates and revisions to the Policy. Any changes will be posted on this page. Please check this page to review whether any changes have been made to the Policy. 

### What Else Do You Need To Know?

This Website is not intended for minors under the age of eighteen, and Axxess does not wish to obtain any information from or about them through this website. If you are under eighteen years old, do not use this Website. Our Website includes social media features, such as “sharing” functions on Facebook and Twitter. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies providing these features, and we do not control and are not responsible for the privacy practices of, or the data available on, the websites of third parties. 

### Key Terms

  * **Tracking Technologies:** Tracking technologies include technologies such as “cookies” and “web beacons,” which are used to analyze trends, administer the Website, and help us provide you with a more personalized experience and improve our services. Cookies are small amounts of text files that are sent from a website to your computer’s browser when you visit the site. These cookies are then stored in files within your computer’s browser. Websites can access only the cookies that they have stored on your computer. For every future time you access a website, your browser sends the cookie back to the server, which notifies the website of the user’s previous activities on the website. Thus, cookies serve several useful purposes, like letting you navigate between pages more efficiently, saving your preferences, and enhancing your user experience with the website. Web beacons (also called transparent GIFs, web bugs, pixels, or action tags) are strings of code that deliver a tiny graphic image on a web page or in an email which is used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the website or sending the email. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information on your computer such as cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, and a description of the page on which the web beacon is placed. In general, any file served as part of a web page can act as a web beacon.
  * **Internet Protocol (IP) Address:** A numerical label separated by periods that identifies every device (e.g., computer, printer) that participates in a network. IP addresses allow these devices to communicate with one another and transmit relevant information.
  * **Personally Identifiable Information (PII):** For purposes of this Policy, PII includes: first and last name; physical mailing address including street name and city/town; email; telephone number; or any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual.

## Contact

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at: Axxess, Attn: Legal, 16000 Dallas Parkway, Suite 700, Dallas, TX 75248.
